blnk.com 2009-03-30

# Help Privacy at BLNK

**BLNK DOES NOT SEND SPAM OR SELL EMAIL ADDRESSES.**

### Information Collected/Tracked by BLNK

#### Information submitted to BLNK

BLNK collects user-submitted account information such as name and email address to identify users and send notifications related to the use of the service. BLNK also collects user-submitted profile information such as gender, age, occupation, location, etc. 

#### Information not Directly Submitted by Users to BLNK

This is information we collect that is not personally identifiable, such as browser type and IP address. This information is gathered for all users to the site. 

### Use of Information Obtained by BLNK

#### Information users submit to BLNK

Profile information as well as photos are displayed to people to support the function of the site as social networking community where users can meet new people. Email address and first names are used when a user invites a friend via email to join the service, when a user requests to add another user to their friend list, and when we send notifications to a user related to their use of the service. Except when inviting friends, a user's email address is not shared or displayed on the site. Users communicate on BLNK with each other through the BLNK service, without disclosing email addresses. We may also use a user's email address to send updates or news regarding our site, but the user may choose not to receive email of this type by accessing their Account Info. 

#### Information that users do not submit to us

We use your server, IP address, and browser-type related information in the general administration of our website. 

### Sharing of the Information this Site Gathers/Tracks

As a matter of policy, except where you are expressly informed otherwise, we do not sell, rent, share, trade or give away any of your personal information unless required by law or for the protection of your membership. However, BLNK may share profile information and aggregate usage information in a non-personally identifiable manner to advertisers and other third parties in order to present to members more targeted advertising, products and services. In such situations we will never disclose information that will be used to personally identify you. 

### Links

This site may contain links to other websites. Please be aware that BLNK is not responsible for the privacy practices of other Web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

### Use of Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a text file stored on the user's hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. Cookies are used to manage sessions on our site. Users must enable cookies to use our site. Also, users may optionally use a cookie to remember their password in order to automatically log in to our site. We do not and will not use cookies to collect private information from any user which they did not intentionally submit to us. 

### Correcting/Updating or Removing Information

BLNK users may modify or remove any of their personal information at any time by logging into their account and accessing features such as Edit Profile and Account Info. 

### Changes in Our Privacy Policy

If we change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our web site so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via email or by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

### Invite a Friend

If a user elects to use our Invite feature to invite a friend to our site, we ask them for the friend's email address. BLNK will automatically send the friend an email inviting them to join the site. BLNK stores this email address for the purpose of automatically adding the respondent to the friends list of the user sending the invitation, and also to send reminders of the invitation. BLNK does not sell these email addresses or use them to send any other communication besides invitations and invitation reminders. The friend may **contact BLNK** to request the removal of this information from our database. 

### Chat Rooms, Notes, Blogs, and Public Forums

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online for example in blogs, forums, notes, profiles or in chat areas - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, by posting personal information online that is publicly accessible, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. 

### Security

Your BLNK account is password-protected. This web site takes every precaution to protect our users' information. We use industry standard measures to protect your information that is stored within our database. If you have any questions about the security at our website, please **contact us**. 

### Third Party Advertising

The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to users by our Web advertising partners. Our Web advertising partners may set cookies. Doing this allows the ad network to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad networks may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. BLNK does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third-party ad servers or ad networks. 

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by BLNK and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertiser. 

### Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please **contact us**.
